{
  "limites_con_raices": [
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{t \\to 0} \\left (\\frac{\\sqrt{t^2+9}-3)}{t^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) } ",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) } ",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) } ",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) } \\frac{1}{6}",
      "correct": "3",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy-medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{h \\to 0} \\left (\\frac{\\sqrt{9+h}-3}{h} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) } ",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) } ",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) } ",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) } \\frac{1}{6}",
      "correct": "3",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy-medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{u \\to 2} \\left (\\frac{\\sqrt{4u+1}-3}{u-2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) } ",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) } ",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) } \\frac{2}{3}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) } ",
      "correct": "2",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "medium-hard"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{t \\to 0} \\left (\\frac{\\sqrt{1+t}-\\sqrt{1-t}}{t} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) } 1",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) } ",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) } ",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) } ",
      "correct": "0",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 16} \\left (\\frac{4-\\sqrt{x}}{16x-x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) } ",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) } \\frac{1}{128}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) } ",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) } ",
      "correct": "1",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to -4} \\left (\\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+9}-5}{x+4} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) } ",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) } ",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) } -\\frac{4}{5}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) } ",
      "correct": "2",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy-medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x+1}-1}{x} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{3}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{2}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{4}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{6}",
      "correct": "1",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x+4}-2}{x} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{5}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{4}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{7}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{8}",
      "correct": "1",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x+9}-3}{x} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{7}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{9}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{8}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{6}",
      "correct": "3",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x+16}-4}{x} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{13}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{9}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{11}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{8}",
      "correct": "3",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x+25}-5}{x} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{11}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{15}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{14}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{10}",
      "correct": "3",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x+36}-6}{x} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{13}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{12}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{17}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{14}",
      "correct": "1",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x+49}-7}{x} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{17}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{19}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{14}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{15}",
      "correct": "2",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x+64}-8}{x} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{21}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{16}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{17}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{20}",
      "correct": "1",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x+81}-9}{x} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{21}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{20}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{19}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{18}",
      "correct": "3",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x+100}-10}{x} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{20}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{24}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{22}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{21}",
      "correct": "0",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+1}-1}{x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{2}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{7}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{3}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{4}",
      "correct": "0",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+4}-2}{x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{5}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{8}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{4}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{6}",
      "correct": "2",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+9}-3}{x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{8}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{7}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{10}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{6}",
      "correct": "3",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+16}-4}{x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{13}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{8}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{9}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{12}",
      "correct": "1",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+25}-5}{x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{13}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{15}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{12}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{10}",
      "correct": "3",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+36}-6}{x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{16}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{15}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{12}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{17}",
      "correct": "2",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+49}-7}{x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{14}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{19}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{15}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{16}",
      "correct": "0",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+64}-8}{x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{18}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{16}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{17}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{19}",
      "correct": "1",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+81}-9}{x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{21}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{23}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{19}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{18}",
      "correct": "3",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\lim_{x \\to 0 } \\left( \\frac{\\sqrt{x^2+100}-10}{x^2} \\right)",
      "answer1": "\\text{A) }\\frac{1}{23}",
      "answer2": "\\text{B) }\\frac{1}{20}",
      "answer3": "\\text{C) }\\frac{1}{25}",
      "answer4": "\\text{D) }\\frac{1}{21}",
      "correct": "1",
      "unlock": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    }
  ]
}